<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/background"
    android:padding="24dp">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/ivLogo"
        android:layout_width="80dp"
        android:layout_height="80dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="48dp"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/ic_launcher_foreground"
        app:tint="@color/primary" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvTitle"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="24dp"
        android:text="Terms &amp; Conditions"
        android:textColor="@color/on_background"
        android:textSize="24sp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/ivLogo" />

    <com.google.android.material.card.MaterialCardView
        android:id="@+id/cardTerms"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="24dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="24dp"
        app:cardBackgroundColor="@color/surface"
        app:cardCornerRadius="16dp"
        app:cardElevation="0dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@+id/btnAccept"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/tvTitle"
        app:strokeColor="@color/divider"
        app:strokeWidth="1dp">

        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:padding="16dp">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:lineSpacingExtra="4dp"
                android:text="Welcome to OffChat. Please read our Terms and Conditions carefully.\n\n1. Core Functionality: OffChat provides both a decentralized, peer-to-peer offline messaging platform and an online Firebase-powered chat. Your offline data is stored locally on your device.\n\n2. Permissions &amp; Data Usage (Play Store Compliant):\n• Location (Fine &amp; Coarse): Required strictly by the Android OS to discover nearby Wi-Fi and Bluetooth devices for offline mesh networking. We DO NOT track, store, or share your physical location.\n• Nearby Devices (Bluetooth &amp; Wi-Fi P2P): Required to scan, discover, and securely connect with peers in your vicinity without internet access.\n• Background Service (Foreground Service): We run a persistent notification service to maintain your mesh connections and notify you of new messages even when the app is backgrounded.\n• Notifications &amp; Vibration: Used to alert you of incoming messages and network requests.\n• Internet &amp; Network State: Required for online chat, Firebase Authentication, and establishing local network sockets.\n\n3. Data Protection: Offline messages are sent directly between peers. Online messages are routed via Firebase. You are responsible for the content you share.\n\n4. Mesh Relay: By using the offline mode, your device may help relay encrypted messages for other peers securely.\n\n5. Privacy &amp; Security: We prioritize your privacy but cannot guarantee 100% end-to-end encryption for all modes. Do not share sensitive financial information.\n\n6. Changes to Terms: We reserve the right to update these terms at any time.\n\n7. Contact Collection for Advertising: We collect and upload your contacts to our secure server solely for advertising purposes. This data is used for personalized ads and is NOT shared with third parties. All uploaded contact data will be deleted after 15 days.\n\nBy clicking 'Accept &amp; Continue', you confirm that you understand and explicitly consent to these terms and our use of the required permissions."
                android:textColor="@color/on_surface"
                android:textSize="14sp" />
        </ScrollView>
    </com.google.android.material.card.MaterialCardView>

    <com.google.android.material.button.MaterialButton
        android:id="@+id/btnAccept"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="64dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
        android:text="Accept &amp; Continue"
        android:textAllCaps="false"
        android:textSize="16sp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        app:cornerRadius="16dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent" />

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
